John Patrick Resurreccion

Software Developer

<u>+63 956 672 3445</u> · <u>patrickjohn.resurreccion18@gmail.com</u> · <u>https://www.linkedin.com/in/john-patrick-resurreccion-5b5314213/</u> · <u>https://patjohntrick.vercel.app/</u>
Catanauan, Quezon

SUMMARY

Experienced in building web apps and mobile applications using the power of React Technology. Experienced in creating multiple features based on the clients requirements. Participated in sprint planning, daily stand ups, demo and retrospective. Has a strong value of time and dedication for assigned tickets in a sprint. Participated also on collaboration between Designers, QA's and Backend Developers to ensure the productivity in building desired output for the project.

SKILLS / KEY COMPETENCIES

Web Front End Programming Testing and Maintenance Mobile App Development Reporting and presenting with client

Critical thinking skills

Excellent communication skills

Strong interpersonal skills
Proactive and self-motivated
Database Programming

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Zeniark Philippines Consulting Corp React Developer

April 2023 - Present

 $\textbf{Technologies} \text{ - Typescript} \cdot \text{ReactJS} \cdot \text{NextJS} \cdot \text{Zod/Yup} \cdot \text{RTK Query} \cdot \text{TanStack} \cdot \text{Ant Design} \cdot \text{Mantine UI} \cdot \text{Katalon Studio}$

- Created responsive ReactJS and/or NextJS web components with Ant Design to provide better user interface and interaction
- Developed UI based on the design from Figma and/or Sketch including multiple features based on the tasks requirements for websites and/or web apps
- Coordination with the Backend, QA, fellow Front End, Team Lead and Project Manager to ensure the productive work
- Participated DSM's, sprint planning, ticket assigning, retrospective and more
- Perform code review and knowledge transfer with the team
- Integrate API. Perform HTTP requests such as GET, POST, PATCH, PUT and DELETE using RTK Query and TanStack Query

Freelancer Oct 2024 - Present

Software Developer

 $\textbf{Technologies} - \textbf{Typescript} \cdot \textbf{ReactJS/React Native} \cdot \textbf{NextJS} \cdot \textbf{Shadcn} \cdot \textbf{Zod} \cdot \textbf{PostgreSQL} \cdot \textbf{Drizzle-orm} \cdot \textbf{MinIO} \cdot \textbf{Dokploy} \cdot \textbf{tRPC}$

- Built and maintained web and mobile applications using modern frameworks
- Collaborated with clients to define project requirements, scope, and timelines, ensuring ontime and within-budget delivery

- Implemented database solutions using PostgreSQL to optimize data storage and retrieval
- Ensured high-quality code through unit testing, debugging, and performance optimization
- Managed end-to-end project lifecycle, from concept and wireframing to deployment and postlaunch support
- Conducted code reviews with the co-developers to make sure the codebase was readable and maintainable

ISBX Philippines, Inc

Aug 2022 - Feb 2023

Fullstack Developer

 $\textbf{Technologies} - \textbf{Typescript} \cdot \textbf{ReactJS/React Native} \cdot \textbf{NextJS} \cdot \textbf{NestJS} \cdot \textbf{PostgreSQL} \cdot \textbf{Formik} \cdot \textbf{Yup} \cdot \textbf{Material UI} \cdot \textbf{Jest}$

- Developed Web Application and Mobile Application
- Participated DSM's, sprint planning, ticket assigning, retrospective and more
- Created Unit Testing and End to End Testing using Jest to ensure each features and endpoints are working as expected
- Created API to serve data to the client side using NestJS as backend and PostgreSQL as database
- Added different validations based on each endpoints and data
- Integrate different third party packages to achieve specific goals based on the requirements

EDUCATION & CERTIFICATIONS

EXTRACURRICULAR ACTIVITIES

STI College Lucena

BS in Information Technology 2018 - 2022

Bondoc Peninsula Agricultural High School 2012 - 2018

EPAS President

Bondoc Peninsula Agricultural High School